[Music]
this thing on
hey miss Potts if you find this
recording don't feel bad about this part
of the journey use the end
[Music]
just for the record being adrift in
space with zero promise of rescue is
more fun that sounds food and water ran
out four days ago
oxygen I'll run out tomorrow morning
I've been when I drift off I will dream
about you
it's how I see
[Music]
thanos did exactly what he said he was
gonna do
he wiped out 50% of all living creatures
we lost all of us
lost friends you lost family
you lost a part of ourselves
this is the fight of our lives this is
gonna work Steve I know it is cuz I
don't know what I'm gonna do if it
doesn't
hi is anyone home this is Scott Lang we
met a few years ago at the airport in
Germany my job really big is just an old
message I know you know that's right
that's me can you buzz me